oneclickdigital.com 2008-02-13

# 

**Privacy Policy**

The information you provide to us through our web site will only be used for your current purchase and will not be retained by us except in our order archive which is used to recall your order if we or you have questions about it later.

We use your personal information internally to improve your shopping experiences and the services we provide. We only obtain personal information about you, if you choose to opt-in to our E-mail list. We may also combine your personal information with third party demographic information data. This helps us to improve the content of our web site and to alert you to new products, services and special offers targeted to your specific interests. Any personally identifiable information we collect will not be shared with any third party.

**Security**

When you give us your credit card number or other sensitive information, that data is encrypted and sent to our computers to be processed via a Virtual Private Network. All sensitive information is encrypted throughout the entire process, and access to this information on our servers is restricted to a small group of authorized employees.

Other security measures include making aware all employees safe security practices and daily review of security measures within our encrypted system.

There are several ways to confirm that a Web page you are viewing is secure. If the site uses SSL encryption, as we do, then you will see either a padlock (if you are using Internet Explorer) or a key (if you are using Netscape Navigator) near the bottom of your browser window. You will also note that the Internet address of the Web page, typically displayed near the top of your browser, will begin with the text "https://" rather than simply "http://" (e.g., "https://www.sitename.com/...). This extra "s" indicates the use of a secure server.

**How Information is Used**

We do not sell or rent your personal information to others. We use customer information we collect only for the purposes of filling orders, contacting purchasers to inform them of their order status, sending promotional information, for statistical purposes and to administer our systems. We may use third parties to help us fulfill orders, to help process payments, to provide customer service, to serve site content, and to administer warranties purchased. We give them access to the information needed to complete their job. Sometimes that includes a portion of your personal information. Our computer systems protect personal information using an advanced firewall server technology.

**Cookies**

We use cookies to help identify you when you visit our store and to customize your experience. The cookie contains a randomly assigned user identification number, the country where you are located, and we may track where you came from, and how you browse our site. The cookies make your use of the site easier, make the site run more smoothly and help us to maintain a secure site. You will be unable to shop on our site without your browser set to accept cookies. We do not disclose your personal account information or any information about your purchases to anyone.

**Store Policy:**

  * All products we sell are brand new.
  * We accept all major credit cards, including Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.
  * C.O.D. accepted with minimum $50.00 deposit by credit card, check, or money order.
  * All checks and money orders require 2-4 weeks for clearance before your order can be shipped.
  * We do not charge your credit card until your order is ready to ship.  

**Shipping Policy:**

  * For your protection, all orders that are submitted to us through our website are subjected to a thorough verification procedure before shipping. Often, this process includes contacting you via telephone or email to confirm your order and delivery information. Please be sure to include a phone number and email address so that we can contact you if necessary.
  * Shipping of items marked "In Stock" is within 1 to 2 days.
  * We will advise you in regards to the delivery date of items not in stock.
  * Sales Tax may apply in N.J, N.Y & C.A
  * If you are buying an item as a gift, please advise us if there is a deadline.
  * Shipping is normally by Postal Service Priority Mail with delivery confirmation but no signature required.
  * UPS ground and Federal Express are also available when that service is preferable to mail. 

**Return Policy:**

  * **Your satisfaction as a customer is our most important goal.**
  * **Time Frame for returns are as follows : - 7 days for Video ( this includes digital video as well ) – 14 days digital cameras - 21 days SLR ( does NOT include digital SLRs )**
  * **Shipping, Handling, and Insurance charges are not refundable.**
  * **All returns must have a Return Merchandise Authorization (RMA) clearly labeled on the return box. Please call for RMA number prior to returning your package. Returns that are not clearly labeled with RMA number will not be accepted.**
  * **Items returned later than 10 days will not be accepted. Special order items which are not part of our regular stock may be returned for store credit only.**
  * **All returns will be accecpted with a minimum of 20% restocking fee, must be in postal money order only!**
  * ****25% Cancellation Fee applies on orders in "PROCESSING" status****
  * ****Refused packages are subjected to a 25% restocking fee****
  * ******Returns should be sent by first class mail with delivery confirmation.******
  * ******If the item is charged by credit card, a credit will be applied to the same account. Otherwise, a check will be issued.******
  * ******All returns must be in the same/mint condition as received.******
  * ******Absolutely No Returns on DJ Equipment,DLP, LCD, & Plasma Televisions over 17"******
  * ******Extended Service Contracts can not be cancelled******
  * ****All cancellation must be done over the phone and not through email****
  * ********If you need additional information, please feel free to contact us at[customerservice@digitalsupportdepartment.com](mailto:customerservice@digitalsupportdepartment.com)********
